Guide to the Reynolds Price Papers, 1880-2014 RL.01050
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Personal papers, 1880-2010, undated
  - Home library, 1924-2010
    - Auden, W.H., 1966 (Box 254)
      George Gordon, Lord Byron; Selected Poetry and Prose (typed copy of Byron's last poem)
    - Baker, Raymond F., 1972 (Box 239)
      Andersonville, The Story of a Civil War Prison Camp
    - Benesch, Otto, 1960 (Box 262)
      Rembrandt As A Draughtsman (inscribed)
    - Bernanos, Georges, 1962 (Box 254)
      The Diary of a Country Priest, translated by Pamela Morris
    - Binding, Paul, 1979 (Box 239)
      A Literary Journey through the American South
    - Bly, Robert, 2001 (Box 239)
      The Night Abraham Called to the Stars
    - Borowsky, Irvin J. (editor), 2004 (Box 239)
      Defining New Christian/Jewish Dialogue (signed by Moody Smith)
    - Brilliance of Birds: The Sculpture of Grainger McKoy, 2007 (Box 239)
      A note and signature from McKoy written on a card that has been removed, and placed in a folder.
    - Brodhead, Richard H., 2004 (Box 239)
      The Good of This Place (signed)
    - Bronte, Emily, 1956 (Box 243)
      Wuthering Heights (annotated by RP)
    - Brubach, Holly, 1999 (Box 239)
      Girlfriend: Men, Women, and Drag (signed)
    - Bryan, Jay, 1994 (Box 239)
      Haiku for Carroll (signed)
    - Buechner, Frederick, 1950 (Box 240)
      A Long Day's Dying (signed)
    - Burkey, David F., 2001 (Box 240)
      Higher Ground (signed)
    - Busch, Frederick, 1986 (Box 252)
      When People Publish: Essays on Writers & Writing (note and signed by author)
    - Cameron, Ron (editor), 1982 (Box 240)
      The Other Gospels
    - Campbell, Roy, 1952 (Box 254)
      Poems of Baudelaire
    - Carmichael, Jacqueline Miller, 1998 (Box 240)
      Trumpeting a Fiery Sound: History and Folklore in Margaret Walker's Jubilee (signed)
    - Camus, Albert, 1953 (Box 238)
      L'Etranger
    - Carter, Stephen L., 2002 (Box 240)
      The Emperor of Ocean Park (signed)
    - Cecil, David, 1973 (Box 255)
      The Cecils of Hatfield House (note and signature from author)
    - Chappell, Fred, 1989 (Box 240)
      First and Last Words (signed)
    - Coffin, Robert P. Tristram, and Alexander M. Witherspoon, 1946 (Box 241)
      Seventeenth-Century Prose and Poetry (annotated by RP)
    - Coghill, Nevill, 1964 (Box 240)
      Langland: Piers Plowman (includes note)
    - Conrad, Joseph, 1956 (Box 238)
      Youth; Heart of Darkness; The End of the Tether: Three Stories
    - Conrad, Joseph, 1958 (Box 254)
      Lord Jim, edited by Morton Dauwen Zabel
    - Cox, Elizabeth, 2001, 2006; 2 items (Box 241)
      Bargains in the Real World (signed); The Slow Moon (signed, note removed and placed in folder)
    - Darien, Peter, 1969 (Box 238)
      Ecliptic (signed)
    - Dean, Leaonard D. (editor), 1951 (Box 254)
      The College Omnibus
    - deBuys, William and Alex Harris, 1990 (Box 262)
      River of Traps (signed)
    - Dick, Oliver Lawson (editor), 1957 (Box 243)
      Aubrey's Brief Lives (inscribed by William Blackburn)
    - Dickens, Charles, 1958 (Box 241)
      David Copperfield (annotated by RP)
    - Dickens, Charles, 1958 (Box 238)
      Great Expectations
    - Donoghue, Denis, 2003 (Box 243)
      Speaking of Beauty (signed)
    - Donoghue, Denis, 1998 (Box 241)
      The Practice of Reading (signed)
    - Dumont, Henri, 1948 (Box 254)
      El Greco
    - Dunwell, Steve, 1983 (Box 254)
      Duke, A Portrait (from Duke University stores employees)
    - Eliot, T.S., 1969 (Box 238)
      The Family Reunion (Introduction and Commentary by Nevill Coghill)
    - Empson, William, 1965 (Box 242)
      Milton's God (signed, note removed to folder)
    - Farrer, Katherine, 1955 (Box 254)
      The Cretan Counterfeit
    - Faulkner, William, 1967 (Box 244)
      Pylon
    - Fish, Stanley E., 1967 (Box 244)
      Surprised by Sin: The Reader in Paradise Lost
    - Gilbert, Sandra M., 2001 (Box 244)
      Inventions of Farewell (inscribed)
    - Good News According to John, 1991 (Box 244)
      A translation begun on 14 VII 1991.
    - Grierson, Herbert J.C., 1921 (Box 244)
      Metaphysical Lyrics & Poems of the Seventeenth Century (from William Blackburn)
    - Gurganus, Allan, 1997 (Box 244)
      Plays Well With Others (signed)
    - Guest, Paul, 2010 (Box 252)
      One More Theory About Happiness: A Memoir
    - Hadas, Moses, 1953 (Box 242)
      Three Greek Romances (a postcard to RP from Jim dated 1964 May 25 was removed from the book and placed in a folder)
    - Hanford, James Holly, 1946 (Box 255)
      A Milton Handbook
    - Harrison, G.B. (editor), 1952, 1954; 2 items (Box 254)
      Shakespeare, The Complete Works; Major British Writers. Volumes I & II
    - Hauerwas, Stanley, undated (Box 242)
      Prayers Plainly Spoken (signed, an undated letter from Hauerwas to Price has been removed from the book and placed in a folder)
    - Hauerwas, Stanley, 2001 (Box 244)
      With the Grain of the Universe (signed)
    - Hayward, John, 1955 (Box 254)
      John Donne, A Selection of His Poetry (signed)
    - Hemingway, Ernest, 1929 (Box 245)
      A Farewell to Arms (inscribed)
    - Holbein, Hans, 1947 (Box 240)
      Dance of Death (inscribed by brother, Will Price)
    - Howard, Daniel F., 1968 (Box 245)
      The Modern Tradition: An Anthology of Short Stories
    - Humphreys, Josephine, 1984, 1987, 1991; 3 items (Box 245)
      Dreams of Sleep (signed); Rich in Love (signed); The Fireman's Fair (signed)
    - Kaufman, Wallace, and Orrin Pilkey, 1979 (Box 255)
      The Beaches are Moving: The Drowning of America's Shoreline (note and signature of author)
    - Keats, John, 1952 (Box 261)
      Selected Poems and Letters
    - Kepler, Thomas, 1952 (Box 250)
      Pathways to Spiritual Power
    - Kitto, H.D.F., 1956 (Box 242)
      Form and Meaning in Drama: A Study of Six Greek Plays and of Hamlet
    - Knowles, John, 1959, 1964; 2 items (Box 246)
      A Separate Peace (signed); Double Vision (signed)
    - Kramer, Larry, 1978 (Box 246)
      Faggots
    - Krementz, Jill, 1972 (Box 262)
      Sweet Pea: A Black Girl Growing Up in the Rural South (signed)
    - Kreyling, Michael, 1987 (Box 255)
      Figures of the Hero in Southern Narrative
    - Lamson, Roy, and Hallett Smith (editors), 1942 (Box 243)
      The Golden Hind: An Anthology of Elizabethan Prose and Poetry
    - Lasky, Jesse L. with Pat Silver, 1978 (Box 255)
      Love Scene: The Story of Laurence Olivier and Vivien Leigh (inside the book there is a pen and ink drawing with the caption, "To Reynolds From Allan 1979 Happy Birthday")
    - Latham, Agnes M.C. (editor), 1951 (Box 246)
      The Poems of Sir Walter Raleigh (from William Blackburn)
    - Latipac, 1948-1951; 4 items (Box 261)
      Needham B. Broughton High School yearbook
    - Lee, Harper, 1993 (Box 246)
      To Kill a Mockingbird (signed)
    - Lubbock, Percy, 1954 (Box 254)
      The Craft of Fiction
    - Lytle, Clyde Francis (editor), 1948 (Box 346)
      Leaves of Gold: An Anthology of Prayers, Memorable Phrases, Inspirational Verse and Prose (note from mother)
    - Malone, Michael, 2002 (Box 246)
      The Last Novel
    - Marrs, Suzanne, 2005 (Box 247)
      Eudora Welty: a Biography
    - Martin, Eric B., 2007 (Box 255)
      The Virgin's Guide to Mexico (signed)
    - Matthiessen, Peter. Far Tortuga, 1975 (Box 247)
      Matthiessen, Peter. Far Tortuga
    - McClennen, Joshua, 1961 (Box 262)
      Masters and Masterpieces of the Short Story
    - McCoy-Thompson, Steve, 2001 (Box 247)
      Weather Boy: A Story of D-Day
    - McGuane, Thomas, 1986 (Box 255)
      To Skin a Cat: Stories (note and signature of author)
    - Miller, Evelyn Ellison, 2008 (Box 242)
      A Clay Inheritance, Poems
    - Milton, John, 1957 (Box 241)
      Samson Agonistes (F.T. Prince, editor) (annotated by RP)
    - Mitchell, Julian, 1982 (Box 238)
      Mitchell, Julian: Another Country
    - Morgan, Robert. Brave Enemies, 2003 (Box 247)
      Morgan, Robert. Brave Enemies
    - Mosse, Ruth, 1989 (Box 247)
      The Wreath Ribbon Quilt
    - New Testament (New International Version), 1984 (Box 250)
    - Nikulin, N., 1976 (Box 254)
      Lucas Cranach. Masters of World Painting. (inscription and drawing by Allan Gurganus)
    - North Carolina State Department of Archives and History, 1972 Winter (Box 247)
      The North Carolina Historical Review. Vol. XLIX, No. 1
    - Oates, Joyce C., 1996 (Box 248)
      We Were the Mulvaneys
    - Old Man Joseph and His Family, 1978 (Box 261)
      Old Man Joseph and His Family: A Play in Two Acts By Romulus Linney (Inscribed to Reynolds)
    - Parker, Harold T. and Marvin L. Brown, Jr., 1974 (Box 255)
      Major Themes in Modern European History: An Invitation to Inquiry and Reflection (Vol. 1), (note and signature from Parker)
    - Percy, Walker, 1976 (Box 252)
    - Perkins, David, 1994 (Box 255)
      The News and Observer Raleigh, A Living History of North Carolina's Capital. (from David Perkins)
    - Phillips, J.B. (translator), 1957 (Box 260)
      The Young Church in Action: A Translation of the Acts of the Apostles, 1957 (a note on a card inserted into the book indicates that this book was once given as a gift to Blue Calhoun from a group called the "QCA Cabinet")
    - Plays of Christopher Marlowe, 1950 (Box 238)
    - Poetry and Criticism of Matthew Arnold, 1961 (Box 254)
      A. Dwight Culler (editor)
    - Porter, Katherine Anne, 1965 (Box 248)
    - Powell, H. Jefferson, 2002 (Box 248)
      A Community Built on Words
    - Price family bibles and texts, 1924, 1932-1942, 1955 (Box 250)
      Includes Holy Bible (embossed, Edward C. Price, Sr., inscribed); Hurlbut's Story of the Bible (embossed Edward Reynolds Price); Wonderful Stories of the Bible (inscribed); Red Letter Testament and Psalms (inscribed); and, a folder of papers removed from the 1924 Holy Bible.
    - Prevost, Abbe, 1961 (Box 241)
      Mono Lescaut
    - Radiguet, Raymond, 1949 (Box 248)
      Devil in the Flesh
    - Randall, Wallace, undated (Box 248)
      Love and Honor
    - Ripert, Eric and Michael Ruhlman, 2002 (Box 345)
      Ripert, Eric and Michael Ruhlman. A Return to Cooking
    - Ruhlman, Michael, 2003 (Box 249)
      Walk on Water: Inside an Elite Pediatric Surgical Unit (signed)
    - Salter, James, 1967, 1988; 2 items (Box 252)
      A Sport and a Pastime; Dusk and Other Stories (note and author's signature)
    - Schiff, James A., 1996 (Box 260)
      Schiff, James A.: Understanding Reynolds Price. Columbia, South Carolina: University of South Carolina Press, 1996
    - Seventeenth Century Prose and Poetry, undated (Box 243)
      Seventeenth Century Prose and Poetry
    - Shakespeare, William, 1958 (Box 238)
      King Lear
    - Selected One-Act Plays of Horton Foote, 1989 (Box 255)
      Gerald C. Wood (editor), (note and signature from Foote)
    - Smith, Grover, 1983 (Box 255)
      The Waste Land
    - Smith, R. T. Faith, 1995 (Box 255)
      Faith (signed)
    - Soliloquy of a Farmer's Wife, the Diary of Annie Elliott Perrin, 1999 (Box 255)
      Dale B.J. Randall (editor) (signed)
    - Spender, Matthew, 1999 (Box 249)
      From a High Place, A Life of Arshile Gorky
    - Spender, Natasha, 1999 (Box 255)
      An English Garden in Provence (signed)
    - Steinbeck, John, 1947 (Box 255)
      The Grapes of Wrath
    - Styron, William, 1952, 1967 (Box 249)
      The Long March; The Confessions of Nat Turner
    - Tighe, Marie Kevin, 2009 (Box 242)
      Arch, Steeples, and Dome (signed)
    - Tin House Magazine, Vol 9, No. 4., 2008 (Box 255)
      From Allan Gurganus.
    - Toibin, Colm, 2004 (Box 241)
      The Master (signed)
    - Tolstoy, Leo, 1956 (Box 238)
      Resurrection
    - Tolstoy, Leo, 1958 (Box 238)
      Tolstoy, Leo: Tales of Army Life
    - Trevor, William, 1992 (Box 254)
    - Valdez, Michael, 1995 (Box 242)
      The Novel and Globalization of Culture
    - Wagenknecht, Edward, 1929 (Box 242)
      Geraldine Farrar: An Authorized Record of Her Career, (from a limited run of 350 copies that were signed by Geraldine Farrar). Inserted in the book was correspondence between Price and the book's author, as well as correspondence from various record collector services to which Price had evidently inquired about acquiring some of Farrar's rarer recordings. These documents have been removed to a folder.
    - Ward, Evelyn D., 1978 (Box 241)
      The Children of Bladensfield (signed)
    - Warrentonian, 1947 (Box 261)
      Warrenton, North Carolina. John Graham High School, 1947
    - Watson, Brad, 2002 (Box 252)
      The Heaven of Mercury (note and signed by author)
    - Watson, Sterling, 1978 (Box 255)
      Weep No More My Brother (note and signature from author)
    - Weber, Bruce, undated (Box 263)
      Bear Pond, galley of photographs with no text. RP wrote poetry to accompany photographs for publication.
    - Weber, Bruce, undated; 55 folders (Box 344)
      Bear Pond, photographs
    - Whigham, Peter, 1966 (Box 254)
      The Poems of Catullus
    - Williams, Oscar, 1950 (Box 238)
      A Little Treasury of Modern Poetry (Revised Edition)
    - Willimon, William H. (editor), 2005; 2 items (Box 251)
      Sermons from Duke Chapel
    - Wilson, John (editor), 2001 (Box 251)
      The Best Christian Writing 2001
    - Woolf, Virginia, 1955 (Box 251)
      To the Lighthouse
    - Yarmolinsky, Avrahm, 1947 (Box 238)
      The Portable Chekhov (from William Blackburn)
    - Inserts and items removed from books and folders, 1950-2010, undated; 15 folders (Box 264)
      Includes folders of inserts and items removed from books and folders including The Brilliance of Birds; Geraldine Farrar; Haiku for Carroll; Metaphysical Lyrics & Poems of the Seventeenth Century; Milton's God; Prayers Plainly Spoken; Selected Stories of Emily Dickinson; A Slow Moon; Surface of the Earth; Three Greek Romances; and, Women in Love.
  - Home library - Price, Reynolds, 1957-2006
    Includes books written by Price, and are arranged chronologically.
    - Price, Reynolds, 1962, 1970-1975, 1980-1988, 2003-2006; 8 items (Box 259)
      A Long and Happy Life (Japanese Translation), A Long and Happy Life, Good Hearts, The Good Priest's Son, Letter to a Godchild (Concerning Faith), A Serious Way of Wondering, The Source of Light, The Surface of Earth (paperback)
    - Price, Reynolds, 1957, 1973-1976, 1990; 4 items (Box 260)
      The Surface of the Earth (inserts removed to folder); The Tongues of Angels; The Good News According to Mark; The Young Church in Action: A Translation of the Acts of the Apostles (note included on title page)
  - Home library - Spender, Stephen, 1949-1978
    These volumes are written by, regarding, or gifted by Stephen Spender, and are arranged alphabetically by author.
    - Cameron, Norman, 1949 (Box 256)
      A Season in Hell (Rimbaud)
    - Complete Poems of D.H. Lawrence (Vol I), 1957 (Box 256)
    - Mendelson, Edward, 1977 (Box 256)
      The English Auden: Poems, Essays and Dramatic Writings 1927-1939. (signed)
    - Oxford Book of Italian Verse, XIII Century-XIX Century, 1952 (Box 256)
    - Penna, Sandro, 1962 (Box 256)
      Poesie (inscribed, "To Reynolds from Stephen, May 1962 Rome")
    - Rilke, Rainer M., 1957 (Box 256)
      The Life of the Virgin Mary (translated by Stephen Spender. Inscribed to Reynolds)
    - Spender, Stephen, 1955, 1958, 1975, 1978; 4 items (Box 256)
      Includes Collected Poems, 1928-1953; Engaged in Writing and The Fool and the Prince; Journals 1939-1983; W.H. Auden: A Tribute. Each is a signed volume.
    - Spender, Stephen, 1958 (Box 256)
      Engaged in Writing and The Fool and the Prince. (Inscribed to Reynolds)
    - Woolf, Virginia: Between the Acts. Rome: The Albatross, 1850, 1957 (Box 257)
      Woolf, Virginia: Between the Acts. Rome: The Albatross, 1850
  - Home library - teaching texts, 1857-1953
    These texts contain annotations by Price, and were used for instructing classes. The subseries is arranged alphabetically by author.
    - Alexander, Michael, 1973 (Box 258)
      Beowulf
    - Fitzgerald, Robert, 1961 (Box 258)
      Fitzgerald, Robert: (Drawing on cover page, annotated by Price)
    - Flaubert, Gustave, 1857 (Box 258)
      Madame Bovary (Francis Steegmuller, translator)
    - Friebert, Stuart, and David Young (editors), 1983 (Box 243)
      The Longman Anthology of Contemporary American Poetry
    - Frost, William (editor), 1950 (Box 258)
      English Masterpieces, The Age of Chaucer
    - Milton, John, 1941 (Box 258)
      The Complete Poetical Works of John Milton, Harris F. Fletcher (introduction), (inside cover note and drawing by Reynolds Price)
    - Segal, Lore and Randall Jarrell (trans.), 1973 (Box 258)
      The Juniper Tree and Other Tales from Grimm
    - Ward, Charles A., 1948 (Box 258)
      Oracles of Nostradamus
    - Wright, David, 1957 (Box 258)
  - Home library - Welty, Eudora, 1965-1994
    These volumes are written by, regarding, or gifted by Eudora Welty and are arranged alphabetically.
    - Aperture No. 81, 1978 (Box 253)
      Eudora Welty; publication includes her photographs
    - Binding, Paul, 1994 (Box 253)
      The Still Moment, Eudora Welty: Portrait of a Writer (signed by author)
    - Cheney, Winifred Green, 1976 (Box 262)
      The Southern Hospitality Cookbook (preface and inscribed by Welty)
    - Fishwick, Marshall, 1972 (Box 253)
      General Lee's Photographer, The Life and Work of Michael Miley. (from Eudora Welty, signed)
    - Welty, Eudora, 1965, 1970, 1972, 1984 (Box 253)
      Delta Wedding (signed), Eudora (signed) The Golden Apples (signed), Losing Battles (signed), The Optimist's Daughter (signed)
    - Welty, Eudora, 1980 (Box 243)
      The Collected Stories of Eudora Welty
  - Home movies, 1930-1956, undated (Box 302)
    Includes early home movies and commercial small frame movies arranged chronologically.
    - Price's graduation, 1955 Jun (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0001)
    - Scraps, 1948 Oct (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0002)
    - Home movies, 1930, 1948-1949 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0003)
      Includes Lula Price; President Truman's visit; and Governor Scott's inauguration.
    - Home movies, 1947 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0004)
      Includes snow; skating; and Sis Belle.
    - Home movies, 1947-1949 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0005)
      Includes Duke games; Macon picnic; and a horse show.
    - Home movies, undated (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0006)
      Includes magicians; and lion and tiger fight.
    - Fields, W.C., 1940 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0007)
      The Great Chase
    - News Parade, 1948 Jan 29 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0008)
      The Royal Wedding
    - Beatty, Clyde, 1948 Jan 26 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0009)
      Animal Thrills
    - Home movies, 1951-1953 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0010)
      Includes senior trip to NY; trip to Nags Head; May Day at Salem College; and, RP and family.
    - Home movies, 1948 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0011)
      Includes family trip to New Jersey shore; and father, mother, Bill, and Marcia Drake.
    - Home movies, 1949-1952 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0012)
      Includes Price family vacations to Nags Head, Crescent Beach, Virginia Beach, and White Lake.
    - Home movies, 1947-1950, 1952 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0013)
      Includes Christmas with the Price family in Raleigh, Macon, and Warrenton.
    - Home movies, 1953 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0014)
      Includes Camp Sequoyah, NC.
    - Home movies, 1953-1956 (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F8-0015)
      Includes RP at Duke; Charleston; Harvard; Ipswich; Raleigh; Italy; Oxford; and, Windsor.
    - Home movies, undated (Box 302, Film-reel RL01050-F16-0001)
      Mother
  - Interviews, documentaries, 1966-2009, undated
    This subseries includes published and recorded interviews with Price, and are arranged chronologically.
    - A Conversation with Reynolds Price, 1966, undated; 5 folders (Box 277)
      Kaufman, Wallace
    - Memphis State Oral History Office interview, 1973-1976; 10 folders (Box 277)
    - Interview #1 with Reynolds Price Southern Writers Project, 1973 Jun 18 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0001)
    - Southern Writers Project, Oral History #27, Interview #3 Price, 1974 Aug 20 (Box 291, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0026)
    - Southern Writers Projects Oral History #27 Interview #3 Price, 1974 Aug 20 (Box 292, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0046)
    - Interview #4 with Reynolds Price Southern Writers Project, 1975 Jun 8 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0004)
    - Southern Writers Project, Interview #4: Reynolds Price, 1975 Jun 8 (Box 291, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0027)
    - Southern Writers Project, Interview #4: Reynolds Price, 1975 Jun 8 (Box 292, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0047)
    - On Women and His Own Work: an Interview with Reynolds Price, 1976; 2 folders (Box 277)
      Rooke, Constance
    - A Great Deal More: Une Interview de Reynolds Price, 1976 Mar 11 (Box 277)
      Georges, Gary
    - Interview, Public Radio, 1986 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0103)
    - A Conversation with Reynolds Price, 1986 Apr 9 (Box 277)
      Miller, Edmond
    - Unattributed interviews, 1988, undated (Box 277)
    - Paris Review interview, 1991 May 26 (Box 277)
      Paris Review interview
    - The Life and Times of Reynolds Price: A Literary Lion, 1999 Oct 26 (Box 277)
      Smith, Rick R. and Miranda Kossoff
    - Charlie Rose Show, 2001 Dec 24 (Box 298, Dvd RL01050-DVD-0025)
    - Oak Room Interview: James B. Duke Professor of English Reynolds Price, 2002 Feb 8 (Box 277)
      Bush, John
    - An email interview for Auburn Seminary newsletter, 2003 Mar (Box 277)
      Bedway, Barbara
    - Price and Charlie Rose, 2008 Jan 31; 4 items (Box 290, Audio-disc RL01050-MDV-0001 - RL01050-MDV-0004)
      Price in conversation with Charlie Rose, as part 50-year celebration of Price's service at Duke University.
    - American Audio Prose Library interview, undated (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0150)
    - Desert Island Discs with Robert Aubry Davis, undated (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0131)
    - Electronic documents, 2002, undated; 6 Files 6 MS Word, text, and wmv files; 84 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
      Includes correspondence; interviews by Speer Morgan and Rick Bader; and, a documentary clip.
    - Interview with night school students, undated (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0132)
    - Reynolds Price: Believer and Heretic, undated (Box 277)
    - Reynolds Price Interview, undated (Box 298, Disk RL01050-DVD-0009)
    - Reynolds Price Interview, undated (Box 294, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0028)
    - Reynolds Price Interview, undated (Box 296, Videotape RL01050-Bcam-0011)
    - Southern Writers Project: Interview #2 with Reynolds Price, undated (Box 291, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0025)
    - Southern Writers Project: Interview #2 with Reynolds Price, undated (Box 292, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0045)
    - Writers & Co: Reynolds Price, undated (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0022)
  - Personal photographic materials, 1880-2010, undated
    Includes Price's collection of photographic materials of friends, family, and travel, and is arranged chronologically where possible.
    - American Rhodes Scholars, 2000 (Box 326)
      Includes Wallace Kaufman, Will Singer, Frank Hielema, Eduardo Morel
    - Anderson, Jeff, and Nicholas Rimell, and Price, 2007 (Box 315)
    - Art Price purchased, 2000 (Box 325)
      Purchased from Royal Athena Gallery.
    - A Separate Peace, 1972 (Box 320)
      Includes Paramount studios production stills and information for the motion picture.
    - Barber, Samuel, 1961, 1970 (Box 312)
    - Blackburn, William, 1951, 1958-1961 (Box 312)
    - Bryner, Yul, undated (Box 325)
    - Class, narrative poetry, 1987 (Box 326)